<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ASA DataFest on DataFest: COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ASA DataFest on DataFest: COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Competition Details</title>
      <link>/details.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/details.html</guid>
      <description>When is the competition? The competition is April 8 through April 22. All projects must be submitted by April 22, 2020 at 11:59p EDT.
Who is eligible to participate? The competition is open to all undergraduate and MS students at Duke.
How large are the teams? Teams can be made up of 2 to 5 students.
Do I have to compete in a team? DataFest is a collaborative competition, so we strongly encourage you to work in a team to honor the spirit of the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataFest: COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge Winners</title>
      <link>/winners.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/winners.html</guid>
      <description>Thank you to everyone who participated in the virtual data challenge! The submissions were outstanding and each provided a unique insight into a societal impact of the global pandemic. A group of 15 judges from academia and industry reviewed the submissions to select winners in a variety of categories. Congratulations to all of this year&#39;s winners! Click below to view their projects. 
Most Creative Topic or Data set emoji_events Dreams in the Time of COVID-19  by Apoorv Jha Write up + Dashboard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources.html</guid>
      <description>Technology resources Accessing software  Duke VM Manage: https://vm-manage.oit.duke.edu/containers
 Access Docker containers for RStudio, Python Jupyter Notebooks, and other analysis software  RStudio Cloud: https://rstudio.cloud/
 Tableau:
 Tableau Public: https://public.tableau.com/en-us/s Tableau Desktop - free student license: https://www.tableau.com/academic   Code repository, version control, and collaboration  GitLab: https://gitlab.oit.duke.edu/
 GitHub: https://www.github.com
 Happy Git with R: https://happygitwithr.com/
  R Shiny resources:  Deploy Shiny app on shinyapps.io: https://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup.html</guid>
      <description>Sign up by April 12 at 11:59p EDT The ASA DataFest: COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge is a collaborative competition, so we strongly encourage you to work in a team to honor the spirit of the competition. If your current situation does not make it feasible for you to work on a team, you can still participate individually.
 Click here to register for the competition.

If you have any questions about registration, please contact Maria Tackett.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors.html</guid>
      <description>We would like to thank our sponsors ASA DataFest: COVID-19 Data Challenge!

The Department of Statistical Science at Duke is nationally ranked in the top 5 research departments and as a top 10 graduate program. The Department currently (mid-late 2015) has 18 faculty, ~45 PhD students, ~70 MS students, ~70 research-active undergraduate majors, numerous postdocs, visitors, and affiliated researchers listed under People. Recognized as the world&#39;s leading center for Bayesian statistics and its interdisciplinary applications, the Department is a Duke campus hub for statistical and computational research.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>